=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 14=
My Demon Core
can serve as a vessel for the Stone.
But you will need the Twin Hands
to extract the Stone
from her and replace it.
Then you can use the Stone
to mend the sky.
And the Core will keep your alive.
Thank you, Elder.
But what are the Twin Hands?
The Twin Hands are a forbidden art
that harnesses the power of creation.
And the one who wields the Twin Hands
is none other than your Huanxi Kingdom's
Queen Zhang.
Little demoness.
Young Taoist.
This path is fraught with danger.
And once the Stone is removed
from her body,
she will lose
everything about you.
If love ends in forgetting...
Then love without reservation
to the very end.
Right now,
the person you want to see
should be able to see you too.
Master has sealed the barrier
completely.
It looks like
he's keeping something out.
Since your master sealed it himself,
that means he must be safe for now.
Senior and Chi Xiao
are still dealing with Xuanwu Sect
and looking into the Twin Hands.
What do we do now?
I know a place we can stay for now.
Hmm.
Yuanchu,
I've missed you so much!
My boy!
Eat up!
Your father's cooking
could rival any fine restaurant
in the city.
You won't find better anywhere.
Oh, and
who is this young lady?
Father,
she is my wife.
You lucky boy!
You chose well.
My dear daughter‑in‑law, come, come!
It's our first meeting.
I didn't have time to prepare.
Here, here.
Here is a little something for you.
So many treasures!
Take them.
A welcoming gift!
You are too kind.
Thank you.
Here.
And this too.
Take it.
I really shouldn't...
Do not worry about it.
Thank you.
Look at you,
acting so formal with your own father!
Not really.
I never had a son of my own.
I took a liking to Yuanchu,
and I'm close with his master.
So I decided to become his godfather.
By the way,
my dear daughter‑in‑law,
when will I
become a grandfather?
That's not up to me alone.
You'll have to ask him.
You decide.
Great!
I am overjoyed today!
I will arrange your wedding right away.
I will invite every noble and official
in the capital.
Everything in the Lu family
will be yours.
Really?
Of course!
You are too generous.
You're so kind.
It is only right.
It's nothing.
Father,
have you seen my Senior lately?
No, I haven't.
I haven't even seen your master
for days.
Has something happened?
Nothing.
Some old friends
are visiting the capital.
Master is in seclusion today.
He's not receiving visitors.
I see.
Don't worry.
Stay here as long as you like.
When your friends arrive,
I'll host them properly.
Thank you.
You are welcome.
Now, let's eat.
Yeah.
Do I look pretty?
You do.
Eat up.
Yeah.
Have some vegetables.
You have some too. I don't like them.
I envy you.
Even though you were an orphan,
you have always had your Master,
your Senior, and Godfather
caring for you.
Now they're your family too.
We'll all protect you
and take care of you.
Hmm.
Do you have any wishes for the future?
A wish?
I cannot tell you.
In the mortal world,
a wish will not come true
if you say it out loud.
But in the Demon Realm,
you have to shout your wish
at the heavens for it to be heard.
Better kept in the heart.
A sincere heart makes it come true.
Keeping secrets, are you?
Fine.
Wow!
(Even if you forget me in the end,)
(I will always stay by your side.)
Ah!
Father.
I will find the killer
and avenge you.
His body was severed.
Who could be so heartless?
It's not just one Bloodskin.
The capital is guarded
by the Demon Hunting Bureau
and countless Hunters.
If it were a demon,
how could it kill so often
without being caught?
Let's examine the body first.
All the flesh and bone is gone.
Only the skin remains intact.
If it was not a demon,
could a human do this?
I've heard of heretics who use dark arts
to boost their power.
But why kill my godfather?
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Whether human or demon,
we've somehow
become the prime suspects.
All we can do is catch the real killer
and clear our names.
I will help you.
Ah!
Are you
human or ghost?
The coroner of this office is my master.
My name is Lin Shuangyue.
When did you get here?
Since the moment
you started examining the body.
So you heard everything
we said just now?
I also know you're being hunted.
(Wanted)
You are not the killers.
How do you know?
If you were the killers,
you would have killed me
the moment I made a sound.
I'll get you inside information.
You catch the killer.
We solve this case together.
That way,
you clear your names,
and I get the reward.
That is a good deal.
So you're a money lover too.
Looking forward to it.
Partner.
(Jichun Healing Hall)
I heard the official killed today
was a good one. He spoke for the people.
But I wonder
why he ended up as a Bloodskin too.
A demon is haunting the city.
The people are terrified.
We need to catch the killer fast.
But this one is too clever.
We have no leads at all.
Doctor Lin,
we have too many patients.
And we still need to
distribute the demon-repelling porridge.
We're shorthanded.
We need more people.
(Still missing two herbs...)
(And a bit more of that...)
We've got help right here.
(Just wait a moment more...)
This is perfect
for hiding your identities.
Great. We've been tricked
into free labor.
Some partner you've got there.
You...
(Jichun Healing Hall)
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter
the hollow fate they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪